https://www.africanfoods.co.uk/privacy-policy.html

Menu
HomeHomeAbout African FoodsWhat's New?
By CountryAfrican American Food, Bold, Unique Recipes To Explore.Afro-Caribbean FoodAfrican Cuisine by RegionAll About African CuisineGhanaian FoodsNigerian FoodNigerian Foods
Site Recipe Index
Slowcooker RecipesCrock Pot Meals
Kitchen EssentialsKitchen Essentials
BooksBringing Africa Home
About UsContact UsAdvertising With UsPrivacy Policy
Email
First Name (optional)
Subscribe
Africanfoods.CO.UK Privacy Policy
At africanfoods.co.uk we are dedicated to protecting your data and privacy.We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use africanfoods.co.uk, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. This will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.Africanfoods.co.uk strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.
About Our Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that africanfoods.co.uk stores on your computer, which your browser provides to africanfoods.co.uk each time you return to the site. We use cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their use of our website, and their website access preferences.Africanfoods.co.uk uses Google Analytics to analyze the use of this website. Google Analytics collects demographic and interest data, and generates statistical and other information about website use, by means of cookies. These cookies are kept on your computer. We share this information with Google, which will store and use this information on its servers. Google's privacy policy is available  here.Africanfoods.co.uk uses information from Google Analytics to track the number of visits to the website, browsers and operating systems. No personally identifiable information is obtained from these cookies. We use the information that Google Analytics generates relating to our website to create reports about the use of the site. These reports allow us to update the site and improve your usage of it.If you do not wish your data to be collected via Google Analytics, you can install its opt-out browser extension or add-on... here.We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our website. These companies use cookies and web beacons in their ads to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. We share this information with these companies, but do not provide them with any personally identifiable information for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information from our website.You may opt out of personalized ads for over 125 different ad networks. ... ..by clicking hereSome third-party advertisements are served by Google. Google's cookie enables it to serve ads to our visitors based on their visits to other sites on the Web. You may opt out of personalized ads by visiting the this page. Google provides more information about how it manages data in its ad products.
Affiliate Products And Services
We receive an affiliate commission for some of the [products/services] sold on africanfoods.co.uk.The affiliate services platforms we use are  -- Amazon, ShareASale, ClickBank, Commission Junction, etc.By clicking on a product or service link, you consent to that platform's use of cookies, as outlined in the link below.Amazon privacy policyShareASale privacy policyClickBank privacy policyCommission Junction privacy policyAWIN privacy policyAfricanfoods.co.uk uses Facebook pixels to determine the effectiveness of some Facebook ad campaigns. You can change your Facebook ad settings here.
Refusing Cookies
You can set your browser to accept or refuse all cookies automatically, or notify you when a cookie is being requested. Taking this action should not cause a problem with the continued use of our site. Consult the Help section of your browser for guidance on how to refuse all cookies or to notify you when a cookie is requested.If you choose to refuse africanfoods.co.uk's cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.
Personally Identifiable Information
Africanfoods.co.uk may collect and use your personal information for the following purposes:To run and operate our site.To display content on the site correctly.To improve customer service.To help us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.To personalize your user experience.To understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our site.To improve our site.To improve our products and services.To run a promotion, contest, survey or other site feature.To send information to you that you agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to you.To send periodic emails, which may include electronic newsletters and/or autoresponder series of emails.To respond to your enquiries, questions, and/or other requests.Africanfoods.co.uk may collect personally identifiable information from you in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you visit our site, register on the site, or fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site.
Specifically, if you subscribe to our newsletter, we will ask for your first name and will require your email address.If you complete a form, we will require your name and your email address, and will ask for information.If you submit content to us, we will ask for your name and email address. Photos you include with your submission, or details in your submission, may personally identify you.If you request to be notified about comments on any content you submit to us, or request to be notified when others submit content, we will require your first name and your email address.If you purchase a product or service from us, we will collect your name, email address, billing address and credit card number.This site lets you share content with your friends and followers on various social media platforms. Below are links to their privacy policies:Facebook  Pinterest    TwitterTumblerGoogleReddit                                                 Africanfoods.co.uk also uses Facebook commenting. Facebook stores all of your comments and may show them on your timeline, depending on your Facebook settings.
You can always refuse to supply personally identifiable information and visit our site anonymously. However, it may prevent you from engaging in certain site-related activities.If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information, we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. We will use personal information received from you for internal purposes only and will not sell it or provide it to third parties.We also collect each visitor's IP address, which helps us combat spam and fraud. We do not use IP addresses for any other purpose.[Website] contains links to other websites that may be of interest to you. However, once you have used them to leave our site, we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information you provide while visiting such sites. These sites are not governed by this privacy statement. Always exercise caution by reviewing the privacy statement of the website in question before continuing to use it.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you whenever you interact with our site. Non-personally identifiable information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about your method of connecting to our site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider you used, and other similar information.
Children's Privacy Policy
This website is directed to adults. It is not directed to children under the age of 16. We operate our site in compliance with current regulations. Anyone under the age of 16 must provide parental consent to use this site. We do not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from anyone under 16 years of age.Release of Information
Release Of Information
If we sell, Africanfoods.co.uk, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale so that the service provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make.
Data Storage
Personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information collected by this site  is stored on our host's servers. That host is SiteSell Inc., located at 1000 Saint-Jean Boulevard, Suite 702, Pointe-Claire, QC H9R 5P1 Canada.If you wish to review your information stored on the SiteSell servers for Africanfoods.co.uk, click on this. You can also edit, download or delete any of your information from the servers by clicking on that link.sSome information is collected by third-party services. These include Mailchimp
Updates And Effective Dates
Africanfoods.co.uk reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our cookie and privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that those practices have changed and provide a link to the updated privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.Agreeing to Terms
Agreeing To Terms
If you do not agree to [website]'s privacy policy as posted here on this website, please do not consent to the setting of cookies and the collection and storage of your personally identifiable information.Your explicit consent indicates acceptance of this privacy policy in its entirety.
Last updated: [2018 June 05]
Want regular updates on African cuisines and food recipes? What about unique health information about these foods - what to eat and avoid to keep healthy from the list of African recipes available? Fill in the form below to subscribe to our Newsletter - AfricanFoods Weekly?Worried about spamming? We are too. We will never ever give or pass on your information to anyone else. We will only use your email address to send you your copy of our weekly newsletter. We do have a zero tolerance to spam. We subscribe to a very strict policy on the handling and use of information we gather on this site! We also get paid for affiliate links on this site. See our privacy policy for further details.
Follow us on social media:
Get Our Weekly Newsletter. Subscribe Today. It's FREE.
Subscribe to African Foods Weekly
Get African food recipes, cooking tips, and healthy eating info  delivered to your inbox every week. Simply fill in your email below and click SUBSCRIBE .
Email
I am at least 16 years of age.
I have read and accept the privacy policy.
I understand that you will use my information to send me a newsletter.
Subscribe
(Your information will not be shared)
New! CommentsHave your say about what you just read! Leave me a comment in the box below.
Recent Articles
Kitchen Essentials List for African Cooking Nov 17, 20 06:03 PMUse this African cooking kitchen essentials list to stock your shelves so you'll be prepared to serve African cuisine at home anytime. Read More
How To Make Amala Nov 15, 20 06:15 PMAmala is a dumpling made from the dried peels of yam. The peel is sometimes combined with dried cassava or plantain. These are then blended to a flour called elubo. Read More
Edikaikong Soup Recipe | Creme' De La' Creme African Vegetable Soup Nov 14, 20 11:49 PMEdikaikong soup recipes is easily the richest of African vegetable soup. It is a soup eaten mainly by the Ibibos and Calabaris of South East Nigeria, but now... Read More
[?]Subscribe To This Site
Bringing Africa Home African Recipes Cookbook
52 Easy African Recipes
You Can Make at Home
[?]Subscribe To This Site
Let Your Friends Know About Us!
The "Need to Know"
Privacy Advertising
How Can We Help?
ContactBringing Africa Home
Hom e  | About Me
| Contact
| Privacy Policy
| A dvertisingCopyright © 2005-2020 Africanfoods.co.uk All Rights Reserved.
Top
